auctionsniper.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy

AuctionSniper.com has created this statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **www.auctionsniper.com**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to reenter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and unique identifiers. The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers are collected to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.

This site contains links to other sites. AuctionSniper.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This site shares information with partner sites that supply services to users of this website on a need to know basis. For example, if users choose to use a third-party service such as picture hosting or payments, this site will share information needed to properly execute those services. This site will not share user information or email addresses with third parties for marketing purposes unless the user has indicated that he/she wants to get marketing or promotional notices.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Correct/Update your account information**  
You may contact support for changing and modifying information previously provided.

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Union ("EU") including the United Kingdom, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR") with respect to your Personal Data, as outlined below. For this section, we use the terms "Personal Data" and "processing" as they are defined in the GDPR, but "Personal Data" generally means information that can be used to individually identify a person, and "processing" generally covers actions that can be performed in connection with data such as collection, use, storage and disclosure. Auction Sniper will be the controller of your Personal Data processed in connection with our Services. 

If there are any conflicts between this section and any other provision of this Privacy Policy, the policy or portion that is more protective of Personal Data shall control to the extent of such conflict. If you have any questions about this section or whether any of the following applies to you, please contact support at https://www.auctionsniper.com/help/support/

**What Personal Data Do We Collect From You?**

We collect Personal Data about you when you provide it directly to us, when third parties such as our partners provide us with Personal Data about you, or when Personal Data about you is automatically collected in connection with your use of our website or services. 

**Information we collect directly from you:** We receive Personal Data directly from you when you provide it to us through usage of Auction Sniper's website or services, such as the following: 

  * Your name
  * Email address
  * Mailing address
  * Telephone number
  * Username

**Information we receive from third party sources:** Some third parties provide us with Personal Data about you, such as account information (e.g. eBay account information). The third party service may send us information about you, such as information from your public eBay profile. 

**Information we automatically collect when you use Auction Sniper:** Some Personal Data is automatically collected when you use Auction Sniper, such as the following: 

  * IP address
  * Device identifiers
  * Log data (i.e. hardware and software information)
  * Web browser information
  * Cookies
  * When you last logged into our website

**How Do We Use Your Personal Data?** We process Personal Data to operate, improve, understand and personalize our Services. As an example, we use Personal Data to: 

  * Personalize Auction Sniper content based on your preferences
  * Bid on your behalf on auction sites
  * Communicate with you about our Services
  * Contact you about Auction Sniper updates or offers
  * Protect against or deter fraudulent, illegal or harmful actions
  * Respond to user inquiries
  * Provide support and assistance with Auction Sniper
  * Comply with our legal or contractual obligations
  * Enforce our Terms of Service or resolve disputes

**What Security Measures Do We Use?** We seek to protect your Personal Data using appropriate technical and organizational measures based on the type of Personal Data and applicable processing activity. For example, we use encryption to keep your Personal data secure. 

** Contacting Auction Sniper **   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, contact: https://www.auctionsniper.com/help/support/

Last Updated: May 2018
